### RUSSEL B. MARCELINO

#32 Crispin St. Rizal Village, Alabang, Muntinlupa City 1772 +63916-421-1017 / +63976-134-7108 russelmarcelino2@gmail.com



## **OBJECTIVE**

To be a part of a reputable organization where I can contribute all the skills and experiences gained from my previous and present education, while enhancing my knowledge and continuously learning and strictly adhering to standard policies in my chosen field.

## **EDUCATION**

2018 – 2022 Informatics College Northgate

Bachelor of Science in Information and Technology

College Diploma, June 2022.

2016 – 2018 Christ the King College of Science and Technology

TECH-VOC in Information and Technology Senior High School Diploma, April 2018.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Sept. 2022 – March 2024 Sagility

Cigna Medical Insurance Customer Service Advocate Muntinlupa City

#### **EXPOSURE**

Dec. 2021 – Feb. 2022 CollarFinder Management Consultancy Inc. (Internship)

I.T. Recruiter

Unit 812 Civic Place Building, Alabang, Muntinlupa City

# Magnaxa Construction (Work Immersion)

I.T. Intern

Unit 1908 Entrata Building, Alabang, Muntinlupa City

# RUSSEL B. MARCELINO PAGE 2

## **CORE COMPETENCIES**

C# (Basic Programming)
Java (Basic Programming)
Computer System Servicing (CSS)
Unity Game Engine (Programming and Design)
Able to communicate effectively through written and oral forms.

## PERSONAL BACKGROUND

Born on February 21, 2000 in Muntinlupa City, Philippines. Understands and speaks Filipino and English. Knowledgeable in Microsoft Office Programs.

Skills: Client and Customer Service Oriented, Programming, Operating and Handling Business, Adaptive, Conflict Resolution, Loyal and Discreet, Quick Learner, Computer Literate and Reliable.

## **REFERENCES**

Available upon request.

I hereby testify that the above statements are true and corre	ct.

Russel B. Marcelino